

ABDULLAH RAHIN

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am Rahin. I am a hard-working and passionate web designer and web developer with 2+ years of experience. also, I have more than 1 year of experience on Laravel. I am highly focused on my work and completed each project as per the given schedule.believe in learning and developing new skills every day to have a successful future ahead.

My main intent is to pleasure the client with my efficiency & efforts, and keep a positive rapport throughout the projects and the connection.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer & Developer at Upwork & Fiverr
2022 - Present

I am working in Upwork & Fiverr as a Web Designer & Developer with expertise in WordPress, JavaScript and PHP, and also done many local clients' projects.

WordPress & Laravel Developer 2023- 2023

I worked at Service Key as a WordPress & Laravel developer For an internship(3 months). I gather lots of experience & knowledge from there. It's helped me to be more proficient in WordPress and Laravel.

CONTACT

+88 018874-97149

ahmedrahin660@gmail.com

🋖 Mirpur-14, Dhaka

https://ahmushfiq.com/resume

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021 Higher Secondary School Certificate (H.S.C)

Feni Collage

2021 - Present Bachelor's of Business Studies (BBS)

Dhaka Mirpur College

SKILLS

- HTML, HTML5
- CSS, CSS3
- Bootstrap | Tailwind
- PHP & MySQL
- Laravel
- Object-oriented programming (OOP)

Front-end & WordPress Developer

2022 - 2023

I'm worked with a team. From there I constantly worked as a skilled web developer with a new experience.

CERTIFICATIONS

Full-stack Web Development

Shikbe Shobai

I completed my full-stack web development .through this course, I got familiar with web technology. I made myself proficient in HTML, CSS, WordPress, Javascript, and PHP.

PHP & Laravel

Shikbe Shobai

I pursued a course to refine my PHP and Laravel skills, aiming to boost my efficiency in backend development.

WordPress Development

Codeman BD

I developed myself as a good wordpress developer through this course.

- JQuery
- JavaScript (ES6)
- Vue Js
- PSD / XD / Figma Conversion
- WordPress Theme Development
- Version Control: Git, GitHub
- Problem-Solving & Debbuging
- WordPress
- Woo-commerce
- Microsoft Office
- Language: English (fluent)

REFERENCE

FAISAL HAMID HIMEL

Mentor, Shikbe Shobai +01715-234605 faisal.hamid.hemel.1992@gmail.com

HAFIZUR RAHMAN

Project manager, Service Key +01814-294661 hafizur@gmail.com